拜托 我想要像在德州赌场那样抓住他
I wanna hold em' like they do in Texas Plays
牵制他 让他盯上我 加注吧宝贝 留在我身边
Fold em' let em' hit me raise it baby stay with me
爱情游戏就是要凭直觉从黑桃玩起
Luck and intuition play the cards with Spades to start
等到他上钩之后 我就要玩弄他的心
And after he's been hooked I'll play the one that's on his heart
我会让他欲火焚身 领教我的本事
I'll get him hot, show him what I've got
看不出
Can't read my,
Can't read my
看不出我的扑克脸
Can't read my poker face
不不不
No, no, no…
看不出
Can't read my
看不出我的扑克脸
Can't read my poker face
不不不
No, no, no…
扑-扑-扑-扑克脸 扑-扑-扑克脸
P-p-p-poker face, p-p-poker face
我们会成为坚强的一对并一起摇摆
I wanna roll with him a hard pair we will be
和我玩一场小小的赌博 这真的很有趣
A little gambling is fun when you're with me
俄罗斯轮盘一但没有了枪就完全不一样
Russian Roulette is not the same without a gun
宝贝 如果是爱的话 不野蛮一点就不好玩了
And baby when it's love if its not rough it isn't fun
我会让他欲火焚身 领教我的本事
I'll get him hot, show him what I've got
看不出
Can't read my
看不出我的扑克脸
Can't read my poker face
不不不
No, no, no…
看不出
Can't read my
看不出我的扑克脸
Can't read my poker face
不不不
No, no, no…
扑-扑-扑-扑克脸 扑-扑-扑克脸
P-p-p-poker face, p-p-poker face
我不会跟你说我爱你亲你或者抱你只是因为我在用我的身体诱惑你
I won't tell you that I love you kiss or hug you because I'm bluffin' with my
我没有说谎 我只是很擅长真爱强力胶
I'm not lying I'm just stunnin' with my true-love-gunning
就像是在赌场里的小妞
Just like a bird in the casino
在你动手前就把你洗劫一空
Take your bank before I pay you out
我保证 我保证
I promise this, promise this
检查一下我的手 因为我可是很不可思议的喔
Check this hand cause I'm marvelous
看不出
Can't read my
看不出我的扑克脸
Can't read my poker face
不不不
No, no, no…
看不出
Can't read my
看不出我的扑克脸
Can't read my poker face
不不不
No, no, no…
扑-扑-扑-扑克脸 扑-扑-扑克脸
P-p-p-poker face, p-p-poker face